let's quickly check if we understood the
right update optimizations suppose that
we have a system with two cores that
uses write-update coherence suppose that
the two cores are executing a program
where core 0 writes something to a
memory address a then core 1 reads it
and this continues so that the write and
then read pattern repeats for a total of
1000 times so this is the first of 1,000
after they do this for 1,000 times this
course go to do something else where
core 0 replaces a and then core 1 also
replaces a the question for you is how
many bus uses do we see when the system
uses no optimizations so there is no
dirty bit and no shared it when the
system uses only the dirty bit
optimization and when the system uses
both the dirty and the shared bit
optimization so for each of these how
many bus uses do we get during this
whole time for block a and also how many
memory writes do we get in each of these
three cases